Aaron Benjamin

Digital UX Designer

Hello, Google.

I believe design is a tool meant to solve problems in the service of others.

In 2010, a systems architect named Scott Hanselman wrote in his blog, "There are a finite number of keystrokes left in your hand before you die." In fact, I quote Scott frequently, especially when asked what exactly a "designer" does. As Hanselman so eloquently put it, "The core function of a designer is to remember this and remind others."

I help clients, big and small, all over the world to better understand how user experience affects their business. Creating a digital experience isn't just building a website or an app; it's discovering why you should offer one and defining who it's for.

My "adult-career-jobby-job" (as my wife puts it) is working with the brilliant minds in HP Inc.'s Software UX team to make some pretty awesome products. I'm responsible for helping designers, engineers, and business stakeholders roll up their sleeves to apply design thinking and creative problem solving to everything we make.

My favorite ongoing project is being a Dad to my little girl. She's a limitless source of inspiration, joy, and heart-melting giggles. She keeps me on my toes and sparks new ideas.

Aaron Benjamin Digital UX Designer

Education

College	Full Sail University
---------	----------------------

Class of 2009 - Salutatorian

Certificates Code Academy - Intro to jQuery

2013

Learn With Google - Using Data (Fusion Tables)

2014

Google Analytics Academy - Ecommerce Analytics

2014

Google Analytics Academy - Digital Analytics Fun...

2014

YouTube DEVTIPS

2014 - Present

Team Treehouse

2015 - 2016

CodeTheWeb

2015 - Present



Aaron Benjamin Digital UX Designer

Skills

Core Skills

Writing

Beginner

Learning

Advanced

Verbal Communication

Moderate

Organization

Moderate

Design Skills

Interaction Design

Master

Visual Design

Master

Prototyping

Advanced

Animation

Moderate

UX Research

Advanced

UI Architecture

Moderate



Skills

Technology / Tools

Adobe Photoshop

Advanced

Adobe Illustrator

Advanced

Sketch3

Advanced

Adobe InDesign

Moderate

Framer Studio / FramerJS

Beginner

Principle

Moderate

HTML

Advanced

CSS

Advanced

JavaScript

Beginner

Jekyll

Moderate

Code Pre-processors (Sass, Less)

Moderate



Work Experience

Graphic Design Consultant

Pyramid Consulting Inc.

Oct. 2010 - Oct. 2011 (1 year)

As a graphic designer with Pyramid CI, it was my responsibility to work with the AT&T merchandising and promotions team to create visual assets for use on att.com, att.net, and AT&T branded social media channels. I designed product landing pages, email templates, catalogue images, and promotional banners.

Sr. UX Designer

AT&T - Digital Experience

Oct. 2011 - Sept. 2015 (3 years, 11 months)

I started with AT&T right out of college and was thrown into the fire on day 1. In my time with AT&T, I was responsible for the Visual and Interaction design of customer-facing products. I worked with many teams over the years working on advertising, online bill-pay, and digital customer service tools.



Work Experience

UX Lead

HP Inc - Software

Sept. 2015 - Present (8 months)

My role within HP-Software is to provide UX design support for various HP products. I work with business units to identify where they are in the development process and help define a path forward to make ideas become tangible products.

